curriculum vitae of

LAURENT **BRUSA**

cell email SO url

+49 1522 9623248 laurentbrusa@me.com stackoverflow.com/multitudes portfolio github.com/multitudes/portfolio https://multitudes.github.io LinkedIn laurentbrusa

Profile

I just finished my two years-long "Umschulung" for Software Developer in Berlin and got certified by the IHK, the German Chamber Of Commerce, in January 2020. As part of the certification's curriculum, I did a 6 months internship for iOS programming, where I developed a museums iOS app for iPad as my exam project. For the exam, I wrote the documentation and held a 15 min presentation in German.

My preferred languages include Swift for iOS, C, and full-stack with React. I also love Python and started to get into Machine and Deep Learning since the summer of 2018. Originally I passed my A-Levels in Electronics and Math with full marks and after working in the electronic components testing industry I went back to the university to study foreign languages.

Later in London, I worked in the Apple Travel EMEIA team as a travel consultant providing travel solutions for Apple corporate and retail operations; I collaborated on organising and ticketing travel and accommodation for various events such as the iPhone's and iPad's launch.

After leaving London in May 2014 I took a year-long sabbatical visiting Japan and South-East Asia. During this time, I took the opportunity to improve my photography and web design skills, and volunteer to teach English to disadvantaged children in India. During my career, I acquired the ability to think outside the box, a robust understanding of working with Macs in a networking environment, and the focus to work accurately and meticulously. I speak and write fluent English and have demonstrable knowledge of several European languages such as French, Italian, and German.

Experience

Aerticket, Boppstraße 10, 10967 Berlin October 2016 - September 2017 Chambers Travel, Am Borsigturm 27, 13507 Berlin July 2015 - September 2016 Corporate travel management for different accounts such as GoPro, Epson, Fossil

APPLE Travel, 1 Hanover Street, W1S 1YZ London January 2012 - May 2014 Senior Business Travel Consultant in the BCD travel implant in the Apple HQ

CWT, Global House 424 Bath Rd, UB7 0EB Greater London 2008 - 2011 Senior Business Travel Consultant

ANA, Hythe House 200 Shepherds Bush Rd, W6 7NY London 2007-2008 All Nippon Airways Airline Reservation and ticketing

Air France Marines Dept, Brent House, HA9 1BF Wembley 2002-2007

Education

IHK Software Developer Certificate at Cimdata, January 2018 - January 2020 Training in Tokyo at ANA headquarters and at Haneda Airport. 2008 Japanese Language Proficiency Test 3 at SOAS University. 2007 Ticketing and fares training by Air France. 2005

"Frei" University, Berlin. Theatre Studies, Music and History of Art. 1995-1998 Humboldt University, Berlin (D). Translator and interpret courses in German. 1993 VIII Technical College, Turin, Italy. Bachelor's Degree in Electronics. 1989

Languages

Fluent in spoken and written French, Italian, German and English.

Swift and iOS app development, C, full stack with React. Python for Machine and Deep Learning. Networks and system administration.